

Ioan-Sergiu Coltan

Entry-Level Web Developer

Aleea Borsec, 4, sc.2, ap.50, Cluj-Napoca, 400408, Romania +0753941656 · sergiucoltan@gmail.com

Sergiu Coltan, LinkedIn, GitHub, Facebook, ADLV

Date / Place of birth

29-07-1988, Baia-Mare

Nationality

Romanian

Driving license

В

Skills

Computer Skills

Software Logic

Programming

Microsoft SQL

Microsoft Visual Studio

Microsoft Visual Studio Code

OOP Programming

C#

ASP.NET MVC

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

Microsoft Office

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Audition

Google Sketchup

Profile

Artist-singer in progress of changing career, for the reason of having a steady job, a more stable income, a comfortable life, and following my second passion in life, which is technology.

I am dedicated, perseverent, attentive to details, very adaptable, experienced in teamwork, very passionate about computers and internet.

I consider myself organized, ambitious, open-minded, self-motivated and I enjoy working in a team or independently.

I have self taught basics in OOP Programming in C#, HTML, CSS and Javascript and I'm very open to learn more.

I recently passed IT Intro test at Scoala Informala in Cluj-Napoca, and was enrolled at the course of .NET Development.

I am very motivated and willing to learn much more.

Portofolio

Here you can find some of my projects: https://sergiucoltandev.netlify.app/

Education

.NET Development Course, Scoala Informala , Cluj-Napoca January 2021 — April 2021

Master's Degree in Canto Classic, Academia Nationala de Muzica "Gheorghe Dima", Cluj-Napoca

October 2013 — July 2015

Licensed in Canto Classic, Academia Nationala de Muzica "Gheorghe Dima", Cluj-Napoca

October 2009 - July 2013

Licensed in Theology, Babes-Bolyai University of Cluj-Napoca, Cluj-Napoca

October 2008 — June 2012

| Fast Learner |
|-----------------------------------|
| Creativity |
| Attention to Detail |
| Artistic |
| Communication Skills |
| Teamwork |
| Self-motivation |
| Problem Solving |
| Ability to Multitask |
| Effective Time Management |
| Ability to Work Under Pressure |
| Adaptability |
| Ability to Work in a Team |
| Coordination |
| Languages English |
| Italian |
| German |

Hobbies

Biking, Hiking, Rollerskating, Gaming, Drawing

Employment History

Artist - Singer, Opera Nationala Romana Cluj, Cluj-Napoca

October 2017 - January 2019

During my time here I had the chance of developing, besides artistic and creativity skills, the fast learning skill, communication skills, teamwork, effective time management, ability to work under pressure.

Artist Singer, Costa Crociere, Italian Cruise Ship

May 2016 — December 2016

Working here gave me the chance of practicing my foreign language speaking, such as english and italian and developing skills such as adaptability, problem solving, teamwork, ability to multitask and to follow instructions, self-motivation and effective time management.

Extra-curricular activities

Tenor Member Founder, Ad Libitum Voices vocal group, Cluj-Napoca

November 2012 - Present

I'm a member and founder of Ad Libitum Voices opera-pop group, that has been active since 2012, with plenty concerts and great presence in social media and television.

Courses

.NET Development, Scoala Informala

November 2020 - Present